<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jedupdate version="1">
	<core_body>
		BwPostman 3 is a complete and extensive newsletter extension for Joomla!® 3.3.6+.
		BwPostman 4 is a complete and extensive newsletter extension for Joomla!® 4.

		**BwPostman main features:**

		- You can compose the content of the newsletter with free text and articles that are already written in Joomla!®.
		- You can use selected content plugins at articles of Joomla!® in Your newsletter.
		- The newsletters can be personalized.
		- In BwPostman you can create as many mailing lists as you want and so you can get different mailing lists for every thinkable constellation of recipients (guests, registered users, issue...).
		- BwPostman always generates the newsletter in HTML and in text format.
		- Extensive template system for easily adjusting the appearance of newsletters. Provided templates may be copied and adjusted or you can create completely free templates for the newsletters (very big thanks to Karl Klostermann!).
		- The campaign manager in BwPostman enables you to combine newsletters to a campaign that belongs together.
		- You can import subscribers from a CSV- or XML-file. So you can i.e. export the address book from a mail program and import it in BwPostman. Export of subscribers is also possible.
		- You can archive subscribers, newsletters, mailing lists and campaigns and restore it from the archive.
		- A special property is the possibility to adjust, how many mails will be sent at once.
		- Sending of up to 20 attachments with the newsletter.
		- Module for newsletter subscription.
		- Module for monthly overview of newsletters in front end with many and varied option.
		- Plugin for enhances personalization.
		- Plugin for subscription to the newsletter while an account for the website is created.
		- For the front-end predefined CSS styles may be overridden by self-defined CSS file.
		- User-defined texts for activation mail and legal information.
		- Webmaster or another person may be informed per mail at each confirmation or unsubscription.
		- Author and created date of articles of Joomla!® may be deselected in settings.
		- Arrangements against subscriptions by robots with a simple maths task or as user defined question, adjustable in settings.
		- Tables of BwPostman can be saved and restored.
		- Tables of BwPostman can be checked and repaired.
		- Templates can be exported and imported.
		- Information of subscriber details can be printed (GDPR).
		- Migration to another Joomla!® Installation is possible conditionally.
		- Detailed manual, further help at forum, both in English and German.
	</core_body>

	<!-- valid links only or leave blank -->
	<homepage_link>https://www.boldt-webservice.de</homepage_link>
	<download_link>https://www.boldt-webservice.de/index.php/en/joomla-extensions/bwpostman/101-bwpostman.html</download_link>
	<demo_link>http://demo.boldt-webservice.de/</demo_link>
	<documentation_link>https://www.boldt-webservice.de/index.php/en/forum-en/manuals/bwpostman-manual.html</documentation_link>
	<support_link>https://www.boldt-webservice.de/index.php/en/forum-en/forum/bwpostman.html</support_link>

	<version>4.3.1</version>

	<compatibility>
		<version>4</version>
		<version>5</version>
	</compatibility>
</jedupdate>
